{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Flat Roof Repair Contractors","__cache./api/resource/task/40395/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40395,"taskName":"Flat, Foam or Single Ply Roofing - Repair","taskDescription":"Repair a Flat, Foam or Single Ply Roof","xmTaskDescriptor":"Flat Roof Repair Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":198,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Flat Single Roofing Roofers wanted","textMessagingName":"Repair Flat Roof","rolloverLongDesc":"Several technologies are used to create waterproof flat roofs, though most firms are skilled in several methods. This category is for when the owner is hopeful that problems can be remedied without complete replacement.","rolloverShortDesc":"Built-up roofs, tar \u0026 gravel, bitumen, etc.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair a Flat, Foam or Single Ply Roof.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Flat Roof Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Foam \u0026 Single Ply Roofing Repair","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":65,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Flat Foam / Single Ply Roof Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Flat, Foam or Single Ply Roofing - Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Flat Roof Project","urlName":"Flat-Foam-or-Single-Ply-Roofing-Repair","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Flat Roof Repair Contractors - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Cost Info, Reviews","searchKeywords":"Flat,Single,Roofing,Roofers,wanted,designs,bids,,prosource,prescreened,national,local,rooofing,siding,,conctractors,roofers.com,roofs,exterior,build,Systems,Rubber,License,exchange,Roof,Ply,Foam","emcCategoryOid":-12061,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":689,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40395/":{"taskOID":40395,"originalTaskOID":40395,"setID":689,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5176,"questionDisplayText":"Roof Problems","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Indicate the problem(s) with your roof. (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6877,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Water leaking into home","answerDisplayText":"Water leaking into home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6905,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Water stains on ceiling","answerDisplayText":"Water stains on ceiling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1059,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Blistering/cracking","answerDisplayText":"Blistering/cracking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6907,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Water standing on roof after 48 hours","answerDisplayText":"Water standing on roof after 48 hours","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1128,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Broken or rusted flashing","answerDisplayText":"Broken or rusted flashing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3141,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Icicles/Ice dams at edge of roof","answerDisplayText":"Icicles/Ice dams at edge of roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3519,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Leaky skylight","answerDisplayText":"Leaky skylight","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5402,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Roof is sagging","answerDisplayText":"Roof is sagging","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5174,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Roof","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of flat roof needs to be repaired?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1174,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Built up/\"tar and gravel\"","answerDisplayText":"Built up/\"tar and gravel\"","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5717,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Single Ply Rubberized","answerDisplayText":"Single Ply Rubberized","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5975,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Sprayed Polyurethane Foam","answerDisplayText":"Sprayed Polyurethane Foam","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5382,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Rolled/torch applied","answerDisplayText":"Rolled/torch applied","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":16749,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":20001,"questionDisplayText":"After Business Hours","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need help after business hours?","shortQuestionText":"Requires help after business hours?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5176,"questionDisplayText":"Roof Problems","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Indicate the problem(s) with your roof. (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6877,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Water leaking into home","answerDisplayText":"Water leaking into home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6905,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Water stains on ceiling","answerDisplayText":"Water stains on ceiling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1059,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Blistering/cracking","answerDisplayText":"Blistering/cracking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6907,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Water standing on roof after 48 hours","answerDisplayText":"Water standing on roof after 48 hours","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1128,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Broken or rusted flashing","answerDisplayText":"Broken or rusted flashing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3141,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Icicles/Ice dams at edge of roof","answerDisplayText":"Icicles/Ice dams at edge of roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3519,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Leaky skylight","answerDisplayText":"Leaky skylight","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5402,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Roof is sagging","answerDisplayText":"Roof is sagging","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6877,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Water leaking into home","answerDisplayText":"Water leaking into home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6905,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Water stains on ceiling","answerDisplayText":"Water stains on ceiling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1059,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Blistering/cracking","answerDisplayText":"Blistering/cracking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6907,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Water standing on roof after 48 hours","answerDisplayText":"Water standing on roof after 48 hours","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1128,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Broken or rusted flashing","answerDisplayText":"Broken or rusted flashing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3141,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Icicles/Ice dams at edge of roof","answerDisplayText":"Icicles/Ice dams at edge of roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3519,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Leaky skylight","answerDisplayText":"Leaky skylight","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5402,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Roof is sagging","answerDisplayText":"Roof is sagging","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5174,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Roof","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of flat roof needs to be repaired?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1174,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Built up/\"tar and gravel\"","answerDisplayText":"Built up/\"tar and gravel\"","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5717,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Single Ply Rubberized","answerDisplayText":"Single Ply Rubberized","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5975,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Sprayed Polyurethane Foam","answerDisplayText":"Sprayed Polyurethane Foam","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5382,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Rolled/torch applied","answerDisplayText":"Rolled/torch applied","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":16749,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1174,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Built up/\"tar and gravel\"","answerDisplayText":"Built up/\"tar and gravel\"","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5717,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Single Ply Rubberized","answerDisplayText":"Single Ply Rubberized","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5975,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Sprayed Polyurethane Foam","answerDisplayText":"Sprayed Polyurethane Foam","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5382,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Rolled/torch applied","answerDisplayText":"Rolled/torch applied","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":16749,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":20001,"questionDisplayText":"After Business Hours","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Do you need help after business hours?","shortQuestionText":"Requires help after business hours?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564376523369pwspr015F22724D8FA4DFF8FD65C05DD318E5A42.pwspr009-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}